Guide to the Time Inc. Index Cards 1933-1993, undated MS 3009-RG 4
New-York Historical Society
- Series VII: Time, 1936-1987; 146736; 134 Linear feet (134 boxes)
  - 1968-1982, 160882
    - It's Good To Come Clean On Health -- Kennedy, Edward, 160905 (Box 142)
    - Kennedy, Edward -- Largewhiskers, Thomas, 160904 (Offsite-box 143)
    - Largemouth Bass -- Los Angeles, Calif., 160906 (Offsite-box 144)
    - Los Angeles, Calif. -- Marshal Islands, 160907 (Offsite-box 145)
    - Marshall Islands -- Missiles - MIRVs, 160951 (Offsite-box 146)
    - Missils - MK-12 -- Munoz Pilona, Carlos Rodolfo (Capt.), 160952 (Offsite-box 147)
    - Munro, Caroline -- New York Philharmonic, 160953 (Offsite-box 148)
    - New York Philharmonic Orchestra -- O'Brien, Vincent, 160954 (Offsite-box 149)
    - O'Brien, Warren S. -- Parker, Everett, 160955 (Offsite-box 150)
    - Parker, Fess -- Politics, 160956 (Offsite-box 151)
    - Politics -- Puebla, Mexico, 160957 (Offsite-box 152)
    - Puebla, Mexico -- Reporters, 161990 (Offsite-box 153)
    - Reporters -- Russia-Relations-Iran, 161991 (Offsite-box 154)
    - Russia-Relations-Iran -- Sea Plan 2000, 161992 (Offsite-box 155)
    - Sea Settlement -- Smith, Howard W., 161993 (Offsite-box 156)
    - Smith, Howard K. -- Stockman, David, 161994 (Offsite-box 157)
    - Stockman, David -- Taylor, Zachary, 161995 (Offsite-box 158)
    - Taylor, Zachary -- Time-Correspondents, 161996 (Offsite-box 159)
    - Time-Correspondents -- Touch of Class in the Heartland, A, 161997 (Offsite-box 160)
    - Touch of Cohabitation -- United States-Relations-Russia, 161998 (Offsite-box 161)
    - United States-Relations-Russia -- Warfield, Paul, 162086 (Offsite-box 162)
    - Warfield, Paul -- Women, 162087 (Offsite-box 163)
    - Women -- ZZZZZZZZZRA, Zachary, 162088 (Offsite-box 164)
  - 1983-1987, 162089
    - A-68 (Protein) -- Allis, Sam, 162090 (Offsite-box 164)
    - Allis, Sam -- Borysewicz, Edward, 162091 (Offsite-box 165)
    - Bo's Going to Follow His Dream -- Congress, 162092 (Offsite-box 166)
    - Congress -- Exchange Rates, 162093 (Offsite-box 167)
    - Exchange Rates -- Heller, Walter, 162094 (Offsite-box 168)
    - Heller, Walter -- Labor, 162095 (Offsite-box 169)
    - Labor -- Motaung, Marcus, 162096 (Offsite-box 170)
    - Mote, Robert -- Politics, 162160 (Offsite-box 171)
    - Politics -- Russel, George, 162161 (Offsite-box 172)
    - Russell, George -- Tanks (Storage)-Mexico, 162162 (Offsite-box 173)
    - Tanks (Storage)-Mexico -- Viet Nam, 162195 (Offsite-box 174)
    - Viet Cong -- Zysman, John, 162196 (Offsite-box 175)
- Series VIII: Time Advertising Promotion, 1923-1971; 167004; 1 Linear feet (1 box) (Offsite-box 242)
  Materials in this series are arranged in their original alphabetical order.
  Time Advertising Promotion includes index cards which act as a directory for advertising campaigns which took place between 1923 and 1971 in Time magazine. Each index card contains a list of advertisements. Additionally, the cards sometimes include information about the edition the advertisement was in as well as memos, research report numbers, direct mail numbers, and miscellaneous notes.
- Series IX: Time Canada, 1967; 160874; 1 Linear feet (1 box) (Offsite-box 122)
  All materials in this series are arranged in their original alphabetical order.
  Time Canada contains index cards that serve as a directory for subject terms. Each index card contains a subject term, a brief description of a topic related to that term, and the date when the topic was covered in the magazine. The topics covered on the index cards include people, places, events, organizations, and objects.
- Series X: Time Inc. History Project, undated; 162854; 3 Linear feet (3 boxes)
  Time Inc. History Project contains index cards related to the research Alex Groner and Celia Sugarman completed for their project on the history of Times Inc. As part of their research, Groner and Sugarman created four sets of index cards. The Alumni Directory contains the names of those who worked at Time Inc. prior to 1958. Books by Time contains books that were either written by Time Inc staff or published by Time Inc in or prior to 1958. The Interview Names Index contains index cards with the names of those Groner and Sugarman interviewed as part of their project. These cards contain the person's name, the topics they were being interviewed about, and the date they were interviewed. Individual index cards sometimes contain the record of multiple interviews that were conducted with the same person. The Interview Subjects Index contains cards that act as a subject cross-reference to the Interview Names Index. These index cards contain a subject term, the name of the person who was interviewed, and the date the interview took place.
  This series is arranged into 4 subseries: Alumni Directory, Books by Time, Interview Name Index, and Interview Subject Index. Each subseries is arranged alphabetically either by last name or subject as per the original order.
  - Subseries I: Alumni Directory, undated; 162823 (Offsite-box 506)
  - Subseries II: Books by Time, undated; 162822 (Offsite-box 506)
  - Subseries III: Interview Names Index, undated; 162820 (Offsite-box 504-505)
  - Subseries IV: Interview Subjects Index, undated; 162821 (Offsite-box 505)
- Series XI: Time International, 1973-1989; 162198; 8 Linear feet (8 boxes)
  The index cards in this series are kept in their original order of two chronological groups: 1973-1983 and 1983-1989. The original alphabetical arrangement within each group is also maintained.
  Time International contains index cards that serve as a subject cross-reference for Time International publications. Each index card contains a subject term, a brief description of a topic related to that term, and the date when the topic was covered in the magazine.
  - 1973-1983, 162199
    - Aaiun Spanish Sahara -- Economy-Spain, 162200 (Offsite-box 178)
    - Economy-Spain -- Long Night of Martal Law, 162201 (Offsite-box 179)
    - Longo, Luigi -- Schmidt, Helmut, 162202 (Offsite-box 180)
    - Schmidt, Helmut -- 72-Hour Document, 162203 (Offsite-box 181)
  - 1983-1989, 162204
    - A&W Root Beer -- Elizabeth, Queen Mother of Great Britain, 162205 (Offsite-box 182)
    - Elizabeth II, Queen of Great Britain -- Merrithew, Jim, 162206 (Offsite-box 183)
    - Merrithew, Jim -- Tanks, 162207 (Offsite-box 184)
    - Tanks -- Zylberztein, 162208 (Offsite-box 185)
- Series XII: Time-Life International Advertising Promotion Index, approximately 1940-1966; 167009; 1 Linear feet (1 box) (Offsite-box 242)
  Materials are arranged in their original order of two alphabetical groups.
  Time-Life International Advertising Promotion includes index cards which act as a directory for advertising campaigns. Each index card contains a list of information including summaries of advertising campaigns and the year the campaign took place. Sometimes research report, promotion, and memo numbers were included. Materials are from approximately the mid-1940s through 1966.
- Series XIII: Unfiled, 1943-1987; 160876; 1 Linear feet (1 box)
  Unfiled contains index cards that were found loose. Based on the original arrangement and separation of materials, the series has been divided into two groups: 1943-1987 and 1966-1968. Within each group, the index cards have been loosely organized alphabetically by subject.
  Index cards in the Unfiled series contain a subject term, a brief description of a topic, and a date. Materials from 1943 to 1987 only contain subject terms beginning with the letters A through W while materials from 1966 to 1968 contain subject terms beginning with the letters A through Z.
  - 1943-1987, 162865 (Offsite-box 123)
  - 1966-1968, 160878 (Offsite-box 123)